edlumina.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Cyanna Education Services

## Privacy Policy

#### Privacy

Cyanna Education Services takes the issue of safeguarding your privacy online very seriously. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for visitors to the Cyanna Education Services website and when you provide information to us (for example when requesting access to a demonstration product). Please read this Privacy Statement carefully.

#### Visitor Information

We require that you provide visitor information when you register for a Cyanna Education Services demonstration product. Visitor information consists of contact information such as name and address. Cyanna Education Services uses the visitor information to provide visitors with access and to track data about utilization of Cyanna Education Services’ services.

#### Disclosure of Visitor Information to Third Parties

Cyanna Education Services will not share any information that personally identifies visitors with any third party (including advertisers and direct marketers) without the visitor’s permission, unless Cyanna Education Services believes in good faith such disclosure is required by law or to protect our rights, or the safety or rights of other visitors or the public.

#### Links to Other Websites

The Cyanna Education Services website may contain links to other websites. As a result, you may be directed to websites that are beyond the control of Cyanna Education Services. For example, if you click on a link or advertisement, this may take you off the Cyanna Education Services website. This includes links to advertisers and co-branding entities. These other websites may collect personal information from you. They may also send cookies to you. Cyanna Education Services is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites and such other websites are not bound by the terms of the Cyanna Education Services Privacy Statement. In addition, if Cyanna Education Services references, recommends or co-brands with any third party websites, Cyanna Education Services requests that visitors to these sites read the privacy statements posted therein as Cyanna Education Services makes no representations about such third party policies. If you feel that a website using the Cyanna Education Services name or logo does not follow an acceptable privacy policy, please send an e-mail via our contact form. We will send complaints to the appropriate third party and may, in particular circumstances, advocate on your behalf to attempt to cause the third parties to change their privacy policies.

#### Submission of Personal Information

Cyanna Education Services operates secure data networks and strives to protect personal information and privacy. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Cyanna Education Services strives to protect personal information, Aegis Learning Group cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information visitors transmit to or from the Cyanna Education Services website.

#### Security

Cyanna Education Services has implemented security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of Cyanna Education Services visitor information from unauthorized access or improper use, and we will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. For ordering transactions, we offer the use of a secure server that utilizes secure server software, SSL (secure socket layers), to protect your credit card information with 128-bit encryption. SSL encrypts all ordering information, such as your name and credit card number, so that it cannot be read in transit. Only customers using browsers that support SSL can complete their order online using secure transactions. Therefore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

#### Disclosure Required by Law

Under certain circumstances, Cyanna Education Services, Inc. may be required by law, court order, governmental agency or law enforcement authority to disclose a visitor’s personal information. Notwithstanding anything in this Privacy Statement to the contrary, under such circumstances or when Cyanna Education Services reasonably believes it is required to disclose a visitor’s personal information, Cyanna Education Services reserves the right to disclose such personal information as is reasonably believed to be required.

#### Changes to the Cyanna Education Services Privacy Statement

Cyanna Education Services reserves the right to make changes, modifications or additions to this Privacy Statement at any time. The changes will be posted here, so be sure to check back each time before visiting the Cyanna Education Services website. We may also decide to notify our visitors by e-mail of significant changes.

#### Acceptance of These Terms

By using the Cyanna Education Services Services and the Cyanna Education Services website, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, do not use the Cyanna Education Services Services or the Cyanna Education Services website and do not provide us with any information. Your continued use of the Cyanna Education Services Services and the Cyanna Education Services website, in light of any changes to this policy, will mean that you accept the changes.
